<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Igor Khapov</title>
    <link>https://khapov.com/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://khapov.com/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://khapov.com/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://khapov.com/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://khapov.com/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://khapov.com/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Team manager and technical expert with more than 15 years of development experience. Blockchain evangelist. Docker and Kubernetes expert. Lead development Data Science Experience Local on Power with GPU support. Filed patent “Portable Dynamic Binary Translated Multi-Architecture Container Images”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cloud advisor. Lead workload transformation analysis project from idea to production as a manager, technical lead and developer. Patent in the cloud migration area.
Speaker on multiple local and international conferences (Blockchain, Docker, Kubernetes, development). Mentor and participant in multiple hackatons. Teacher for the German development lab and IBM clients. Technical expert for many local client engagements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert in DevOps area. Lead DevOps stream in bank audit project. Ability to develop DevOps process from scratch.
People and project manager with more than 5 years experience. High level of PM skills and experience to work as technical lead of the project. MBA with project management focus.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>https://khapov.com/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://khapov.com/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
